Deborah Dickerson, PhD

Associate Professor at Virginia Tech

Summary

Associate professor at Virginia Tech and President of Dickerson Environmental Consulting. Expertise areas: control of pollutants arising from the built environment (lead, asbestos, radon, dust), facility maintenance management, pollution prevention, environmental site assessment, and process design.

Experience

Associate Professor of Civil and Environmental Engineering at Virginia Tech

June 2015 - Present

Research interests: control of pollutants arising from construction operations and the built environment. Healthy Homes and Schools. Pollution Prevention Planning. Prevention through Design innovations to control hazards.

President and CEO

August 2014 - Present

Providing consultation, design, training, and expert witness services in the areas of industrial hygiene, environmental compliance, and industrial process system design.

www.dickersonenvironmental.com

Assistant Professor at Virginia Tech

August 2007 - June 2015 (7 years 11 months)

Education

Virginia Tech

PhD, Industrial Engineering, 2004 - 2007

North Carolina State University

Master of Science (M.S.)

Deborah Dickerson, PhD

Associate Professor at Virginia Tech



Contact Deborah on LinkedIn